NOUR **KHALAYLE**

A GRADUATE ENGINEER SOFTWARE TESTER

Hey, I'm Nour, 20 years old Graduated from Smart Academy College QA Engineer (manual & automation). ISTQB certification. Ability to learn quickly, often in high-pressure situations to fully understand a new product, platform, or any mixture of the two, I have many projects on the server, and I know a lot of programming languages





https://www.linkedin.com/in/nour-khalayle-799753224/

PROJECTS

The First project:

It was in MTM Test real software and websites and write test documents.

The Second project:

It was in the JIRA Group project in Jira, checking test status, writing STP, STD documents, and doing tests for different sites.



My Website:

https://nooraldenchating.000webhostapp.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE

15/3 - 27/3 Smart Group with Carbyne Company

System test Volunteer project with Carbyne Company, 991 system for an emergency with college.

7/2021 - Present Freelancer Tester, UTest

Test software or websites offered on UTEST.

4/2019 - Present Selling Projects, Upwork

Programming websites and selling personal projects, Website design

2018 - 2019 food preparation, Mcdonal'z

Different work, whether in the kitchen or outside

CONTACT



052-2799242



nooralden.12.n@gmail.com



driver's license: B. C1

EDUCATION

March 2021 - October 2021

Smart College, Tel-Aviv

Manual Software Tester MTM & JIRA

Testing Documents STP STD STR

Testing methodologies and all types of tests Agile Language SQL high level.

Linux, Windows, Mac Server Administration Automation Selenium high level Quality assurance engineer certificate

COURSES

- CYBER and information security course(96)
- Linux System Administrator(85)
- Tester Automation Software Selenium(86)
- OOP JAVA Algorithms

2014 - 2017

Diploma(Full Units), HIGH SCHOOL ATID, Taibe Certificate of graduation full units

SKILLS

